When looking at Western Europe, we don't usually think about poverty – but in fact, some people in modern-day Britain are so hard up that they can't afford to buy food.
当我们审视西欧时，通常不会想到贫困——但实际上，现如今一些英国人经济拮据，以至于买不起食物。
Back in 2008, the financial crisis caused a lot of redundancies.
早在2008年，金融危机导致了许多人被裁员。
Then there were the cuts to the welfare system in 2013 which added to the problem – and many British people fell into debt.
然后是2013年福利制度的削减，这加剧了问题——许多英国人负债累累。
It's estimated that 500,000 people in the UK have turned to food banks, just to get by.
据估计，英国有50万人求助于食品银行，只为勉强维持生计。
Steph Hagen, who works in a Nottingham food bank, says: "People do not go to a food bank because it's an open door.
在诺丁汉食品银行工作的斯蒂芬·哈根说：“人们去食品银行并不是因为它敞开大门。
It's a case of they go to it because they need to.
而是因为他们不得不去。
With our food bank – we are an independent one, and we have limited stocks – everyone who comes through our door has no income whatsoever."
我们的食品银行是独立的，库存有限——每个来我们这里的人都没有任何收入。”
There are checks and referrals to make sure nobody is abusing the system.
检查和推荐机制确保没有人滥用该系统。
If a doctor or a social worker thinks someone needs to use a food bank – even for a short time – they can give them vouchers.
如果医生或社工认为某人需要使用食品银行——即使是短期的——他们可以给他们发放代金券。
Then the people in need take the vouchers along to the food bank and they get handouts for three days.
然后，有需要的人带着代金券去食品银行，领取三天的救济品。
Churches and individual donors provide most of the food in the banks.
教堂和个人捐赠者提供了食品银行的大部分食物。
But some businesses might help out too.
但一些企业也可能提供帮助。
And what sort of food is offered in food banks?
食品银行提供什么样的食物？
Hagen says: "Basically, we've got porridge.
哈根说：“基本上，我们有粥。
We do occasionally get fresh produce but it's very rare, especially in the winter months.
我们偶尔会得到新鲜农产品，但这非常罕见，尤其是在冬季。
It's like, tinned fruit, tinned ready meals.
比如罐头水果、罐头即食餐。
We have to give out 'no-cooking' food parcels because people can't afford the gas and electricity".
我们必须分发‘无需烹饪’的食品包裹，因为人们负担不起煤气和电费。”
Community spirit has a lot to do with food banks.
社区精神与食品银行有很大关系。
Volunteers say they are a great meeting place for people who are lonely and depressed.
志愿者们说，食品银行是孤独和沮丧的人们一个很好的聚集地。
And when facing a crisis, some beneficiaries might need to feed not only their belly – but also their soul.
而在面对危机时，一些受益者可能不仅需要填饱肚子——还需要抚慰心灵。